[{"answer": "Touch that phone, kid, and you lose your left nut. my friend raises his hands.", "docId": "Youth-in-Revolt.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I don't want the Lincoln. I want my nin", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Then for God's sake, my friend, just sell the my friend and pay them", "docId": "Youth-in-Revolt.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "What code? The vehicular code", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Can't. It's in The Code", "docId": "Youth-in-Revolt.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Code of the streets, Babe. Code of the streets", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Did you mean it, my friend? A beat as he is lost in the ocean of her gaze before he manages to gain his senses", "docId": "Youth-in-Revolt.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You can read it if you'd like", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "How so", "docId": "Youth-in-Revolt.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Brilliant. Not that I'm fond of that place, but I'd live in a drainage culvert to be with you", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "my friend, there are more important things in life than money", "docId": "Youth-in-Revolt.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I've got two words for you. Safe sex", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Not lately. But he's missed several child support payments, and is not looking for work. So now I'm going to public school in that place", "docId": "Youth-in-Revolt.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Yes. And he's had an offer from a respectable publication in that place", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "My mom is paying for your therapy", "docId": "Youth-in-Revolt.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Yes, but it was your idea", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I guess so. It was your cyclops I was staring at", "docId": "Youth-in-Revolt.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "That's true. Gee, maybe I am gay", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Mom? Do you think it might be a good idea if I moved in with him", "docId": "Youth-in-Revolt.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "But shouldn't you depend on the child support money for, you know... child support", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " Psst. my friend. my friend finds Lefty lurking in the shrubs that divide his mother's lawn from the neighbor's. He limps to his friend", "docId": "Youth-in-Revolt.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "No. I did not get to blow my wad", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "May I sit at your table", "docId": "Youth-in-Revolt.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I am my friend. my friend sits and shakes their hands", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "You just missed him, my friend. He just grabbed a couple condoms and left", "docId": "Youth-in-Revolt.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I think he said he was going to my friend's room", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "It's not my fault, you tigh", "docId": "Youth-in-Revolt.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Does it bother you that you're a selfish, uptight, boring lover", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Let's go, my friend. my friend, I'll pick up the rest of my things tomorrow", "docId": "Youth-in-Revolt.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I paid you all your money", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": " my friend? my friend turns to find Lefty coming up the path with two bags of groceries under his arms", "docId": "Youth-in-Revolt.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "my friend, haven't you heard? my friend's been arrested", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "You can stay here a couple days, but eventually they'll come looking for you. I don't have much money to give you, but here. my friend takes the wad of cash, clearly moved", "docId": "Youth-in-Revolt.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I love you too, you little brat", "qsentId": 34}]